Earl Browder Papers
Earl Browder Papers
- Writings
  - Articles
    - 1942 Jun-Dec (Box 47)
      The U.S.-U.S.S.R. Alliance - Is It An Accident?, The Worker, 6/14/1942
      The Anglo-Soviet-American Alliance and the Anniversary of June 22nd, The Communist, 6/14/1942
      Some Political Problems Of The Pacific Front, The Worker, 6/21/1942
      U.S. Economy Must Still Be Mobilized For War, 6/23/1942
      The Threat Against Unity in the South, The Worker, 8/16/1942
      Browder Accuses State Dep't Clique, The Worker, 10/4/1942
      Questions and Answers, 10/16/1942
      How the Press Treated the Welles Memorandum, 10/25/1942
      For Victory and a Lasting Peace, Liberty, 10/28/1942
      Building the Press, Party News, 10/1942
      on the role of white collar uniions in the war effort, The Communist, 11/1942
      A Wage and Production Policy for American labor, 11/27/1942
      Centralized Control of War Production, The Daily Worker, 11/30/1942
      Browder Emphasizes Urgency of Attaining Goal, 11/30/1942
      Twenty Five Years Of Soviet Power, 11/1942
      All-Out War Production for All-Out Offensive, The Daily Worker, 12/6/1942
      Earl Browder Discusses Unions in Wartime, The Daily Worker, 12/17/1942
      Storm Signals: The People Must Know and Act, The Worker, 12/27/1942
    - 1943 (Box 47)
      A Monopoly Capitalist Looks At The Future (two articles), circa 1943
      Russia, The United States and the Communist Party, circa 1943
      Questions re: Labor and War Production, 1943
      Questions and answers re: Second Front, 1943
      Questions and answers re: American politics, 1943
      The Carrot and the Club or The Copperhead Cabal, 1943
      The Education of Wendell Willkie, review of One World by Wendell Willkie, 1943
      Moscow Conference of Foreign Ministers, 1943
    - 1943 Jan-Dec (Box 47)
      A Different Kind of Party, The Worker, 1/3/1943
      The Manpower Problem in Agriculture, 1/8/1943
      Browder Discusses Colonial Question; Soviet Union, and Post-War Policing, The Daily Worker, 1/14/1943
      The Decisive Turn in the War, The Worker, 1/24/1943
      Significance of Casablanca and Our Duties, 2/13/1943
      Interview with Miss L. Rixey, Life, 3/3/1943
      Defeatist Attack on Soviet Alliance Menaces Victory, The Worker[?], 3/7/1943
      Browder's Reply to Head of Ford Local, Detroit News[?], 3/14/1943
      Wage policy in War Production, The Worker, 3/14/1943
      The Mine Strike and Its Lessons, The Worker[?], 5/8/1943
      Wage Policy in War Production, The Worker, 5/14/1943
      The Strike Wave Conspiracy, article based on May 14, 1943 speech, 5/14/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 5/26/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Tribune, 5/31/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 5/31/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 6/6/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 6/15/1943
      Hold the Home Front, The Worker, 6/20/1943
      Communist Bogey Hit By Decision - Browder, press statement, 6/22/1943
      Questions and Answers: election, 6/22/1943
      Questions and Answers: art and the war, 6/22/1943
      The Artist and the War, 6/23/1943
      Questions and Answers re: World Peaceways Program, World Peaceways, Inc., New York, 7/8/1943
      Letter to the editor, The Nation, 7/12/1943
      Questions and Answers in Browder broadcast on Communist Party, The Worker, 7/14/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 7/16/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 7/29/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 8/1/1943
      A Case History of Liberal Integrity, New Masses, 8/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 8/16/1943
      Answer to Dr Meiklejohn, New Masses, 9/1943
      Reply to the reply of Dr. Meiklejohn, New Masses, 9/1943
      Questions and Answers, 9/2/1943
      Questions and Answers: Manhattan Center Meeting, 9/2/1943
      Incentive Wage Key to War Labor Problems, The Worker, 9/5/1943
      The Quebec Conference and the Future of the Anglo-Soviet-American Coalition, The Worker, 9/5/1943
      The Future of the Anglo-Soviet-American Coalition, Chicago Daily News, 9/9/1943
      Hitler's Uprisings in the United States, 9/12/1943
      Hitler's Uprisings in America, New Masses, 9/14/1943
      Browder Speech at Cacchione Rally, Daily Worker, 10/1943
      Victory Has a Price, New Masses, 10/5/1943
      Letter to the editor, New Masses, 10/6/1943
      The Tenth Anniversary of Dimitroff's Blow to Nazism, The Worker, 10/10/1943
      Nonpartisan Youth Organization Replaces Young Communist League, United Press, 10/12/1943
      Answer to Dr Meiklejohn, New Masses, 10/19/1943
      On the 26th Anniversary of Soviet Power and the 10th Anniversary of Soviet-American Diplomatic Relations, 11/1943
      Cooperation with Communists, New Masses, 11/16/1943
      Free Speech for Fascists?, New Masses, 12/7/1943
      Letter to the editor, Peoples' Voice, 12/19/1943
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 12/24/1943
      The Three Power Conference At Moscow, The Communist, 12/1943
    - 1944 (Box 47)
      Book review: Basic Writings of Thomas Jefferson by Philip S. Foner, ed., 1944
      American Masses and the Russian-Polish Relations, circa 1944
      More Unity and More Work, circa 1944
      The American Way of Life, Readers Scope, 1944
      Communist? So What?, 1944
      The Political Program of Native American Fascism, 1944
      Book review: America Unlimited by Eric Johnston, New Masses, 1944
      Book review: As We Go Marching by John T. Flynn, 1944
    - 1944 Jan-Dec (Box 47)
      Marxism Arms Communists to Meet and Solve Issues Today, The Worker, 1/9/1944
      Teheran: History's Greatest Turning Point, Communist, 1/1944
      Strengthen National Unity, The Worker, 1/16/1944
      Browder Reveals Adolph Berle's Intrigues in South America, The Worker[?], 1/21/1944
      Teheran and the Future, New Masses, 1/25/1944
      The Readers Ask, New Masses, 2/8/1944
      Election Must Aid Unity - Browder, The Daily Worker, 2/1/1944
      Dream Come True - and Teheran (Art Young Memorial), New Masses, 2/15/1944
      For Victory and a Lasting Peace, Liberty Magazine, 2/26/1944
      Browder Interviews PM, The Worker, 3/26/1944
      Partisanship - A Luxury America Cannot Afford, The Communist, 3/1944
      Letter to the editor, The Nation, 4/18/1944
      Freiheit Great National Asset Browder Says on 22nd Year, The Worker, 4/26/1944
      Letter to the editor, CBS, 4/27/1944
      Lowell Mellett, 5/14/1944
      Letter to the editor (2 versions), Salt Lake City Desert News, 5/16/1944
      Teheran, Report to the National Convention CPUSA, 5/20/1944
      Text of Browder's Convention Report, The Daily Worker, 5/22/1944
      Press release, Transradio, 5/1944
      Letter to the editor, The Nation, 6/6/1944
      Close Nation's Ranks, Communists Call, The Daily Worker, 6/7/1944
      The War and the Elections, The Worker, 6/18/1944
      Hold the Home Front!, Communist, 7/1/1944
      Book review: America Unlimited by Eric Johnston, New Masses, 8/29/1944
      Anna Damon - A Great American Woman, 9/?/1944
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 9/25/1944
      Text of Browder's Garden Speech, The Daily Worker, 9/29/1944
      The War and the Elections, The Worker, 10/1/1944
      Dewey Disunity Drive Menaces War - Browder, The Worker, 10/1/1944
      Letter to the editor, Dallas Morning News, 10/2/1944
      Browder Nails Lewis for Strike Incitement, The Daily Worker, 10/9/1944
      Wendell Willkie, 10/9/1944
      Browder Tells YCL Rally Role of Morale in Victory, The Daily Worker, 10/16/1944
      Freedom of Comment, The Economist, 10/21/1944
      Cooperation Between the USA and the USSR, The Daily Worker, 11/7/1944
      The Nature of the Coalition, New Masses, 11/9/1944
      Vote Clears the Way for Quick Victory: Browder, The Daily Worker, 11/9/1944
      Browder Tells How Worker Will Spur Greater Unity, The Worker, 11/20/1944
      Hitler's Shadow Over the Nation, Freedom (Morning Freiheit), 11/25/1944
      Continue '44 Unity in City Elections: Browder, The Daily Worker, 11/29/1944
      Questions and Answers, 11/29/1944
      On the Election Results, New Masses, 12/1944
      Browder Answers N.Y. Times Slander..., 12/12/1944
      Dimitroff, the Champion of World Democratic Unity, The Worker, 12/23/1944
      November 7 and the Future, New Masses, 12/26/1944
    - 1945 (Box 48)
      Why Dorothy Thompson Wants a Soft Peace, circa 1945
      The Big Three in Crimea, Political Affairs, 1945
      Economic Policy of the New Bulgaria, More on the New Poland's Economic Policy, 1945
      A Quarter Century Of The American Communist Movement, 1945
    - 1945 Jan-Dec (Box 48)
      The Study Of Lenin's Teachings, Political Affairs, 1/1945
      November 7 and the Future: II, New Masses, 1/2/1945
      Press releas on Stalin's Feb 9 speech, 2/1945
      letter to Reader's Forum, New Masses, 3/20/1945
      Defeatist Trends on the Left, New Masses, 4/3/1945
      Toward the Organization of World Peace, 4/7/1945
      Press release on Death of Roosevelt, 4/12/1945
      Toward the organization of world peace, The Worker, 4/15/1945
      Why Worker and Daily Worker are Indispensable, Daily Worker, 4/30/1945
      The American Way of Life, Reader's Scope, 5/1945
      Roosevelt's Heritage And The Task Ahead, Political Affairs, 5/1945
      Introduction to Engels' Socialism Utopian and Scientific, 5/1/1945
      A Foreword to the Article of Jacques Duclos (with Russian translation), Daily Worker, 5/24/1945
      The San Francisco Conference, 5/28/1945
      After V-E Day - What Next?, Political Affairs, 6/1945
      Soviet-American Relations: Is It War or Peace? (with Russian translation), 6/2/1945
      Questions and Answers: Manhattan Center, 6/4/1945
      Tasks of the American Working Class After V-E Day (Russian translation), 6/18/1945
      Speech at the National Committee Meeting (Russian translation), 6/18/1945
      On The Question Of Revisionism (with Russian translation), 7/15/1945
      Speech at the National Convention of the Communist Political Association (Russian translation), 7/26/1945
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 12/19/1945
    - May 24 - July 26, 1945 (Box 48)
      A Foreword to the Article of Jacques Duclos
      Soviet-American Relations: Is It War Or Peace?
      Speech at the National Committee Meeting
      On the Question Of Revisionism
      Speech at the National Convention of the Communist Political Association
      Appeal Against Order of Expulsion from the Party
    - 1946 (Box 48)
      Important points to use in a review of M. N. Roy's Mission to China, 1946
      The U.S. And The U.S.S.R. Can Organize aDurable Peace, circa 1946
      Was The Commintern Really Dissolved?, circa 1946
      Accumulation of Idle Capital in the U.S., 1946
      Adventure in Finland, 1946
      The Iron Curtain: What It Is and What's Behind It, 1946
    - 1946 Feb-Dec (Box 48)
      Open letter to CP members (with Russian translation), Daily Worker, 2/8/1946
      Permanent Peace or a New War?, New Republic, 8/5/1946
      Russia reconverts, New Republic, 8/12/1946
      The Soviet Union and Its Neighbors, New Republic, 8/19/1946
      An American Loan to thr USSR, New Republic, 8/26/1946
      Everyday Life in Russia, New Republic, 9/2/1946
      Peace or War with Russia?, New Republic, 9/9/1946
      Letter to the editor in reply to a letter from William Z. Foster, New York Times, 9/26/1946
      Are American Communists a Threat to Labor Unions, Town Meeting, 10/24/1946
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 11/1946
      Progress toward peace and disarmament, 12/15/1946
    - 1947 (Box 48)
      Memorandum on History of the Labor Movement in the United States by Philip Foner, 1947
      Satlin's Denunciation Of Churchill, circa 1947
      The State of American Foreign policy (Lawyers Guild), memorandum, circa 1947
      First Fruits of the Duclos Intervention, 1947
      A Reply to Alexander Bitelman, 1947
      Letter to the editor, Look, 2/15/1947
      The Problems of the French Union, Humanity, 4/9/1947
    - 1948 (Box 48)
      The Postwar Crisis and the New Party, circa 1948
      The Need for a Thorough Marxist Understanding of America, Monthly Review, 1948
      Operation X and the Upheaval In Bogota, 1948
      What Happens With the Wallace Movement?, 1948
      Outline for Discussion re: 1948 elections, 1948
    - 1948 Jan-Nov (Box 48)
      World Communism and American Foreign Policy, 1/1948
      Answer to Vronsky, For a Lasting Peace, For a People's Democracy, Belgrade, Yugoslavia, 5/3/1948
      Book review: One Thousand Americans by George Seldes, Pravda, 6/29/1948
      Letter to the editor, Daily Worker, 7/1/1948
      Training of Leading Party and Soviet Cadres, Pravda, 7/7/1948
      Letter to the editor, New York Herald Tribune, 7/16/1948
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 10/5/1948
      Some aspects of the American Elections, Pravda[?], 11/1948
    - 1949 (Box 48)
      The Foster-Williamson Letter Answered, circa 1949
      Is There an American Peace policy?, circa 1949
      Progressive America, circa 1949
      Foster's 'New Route' to Socialism, 1949
      The Light That Failed, 1949
      Press release- Open letter to National Committee, CPUSA, 3/23/1949
    - 1950 (Box 49)
      The Contempt of Congress Issue, Daily Worker, 1950
      An Analysis of Varga's Self-Criticism, 1950
      response to Walter Winchell's "Question Marks???", 1950
      Language and War, 1950
      The Communists and the State Department, 1950
      The 'Contempt of Congress' Issues (incomplete), 1950
      Senate testimony: exchange with Sen. Hickenlooper, 1950
    - 1950 Apr-Nov (Box 49)
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 4/6/1950
      Failure of Socialism in America, 4/18/1950
      China, the State Department and the Communists, 4/22/1950
      Browder Says Budenz Lies on China Policy, The Daily Compass, 4/26/1950
      Comments on CIO Speakers Book of Facts, 5/20/1950
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 9/20/1950
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 9/21/1950
      Why Reactionaries Won The 1950 Elections, 11/1950
    - 1951 (Box 49)
      The Meaning of MacArthur, 1951
      letter to the editor, The Nation, 3/10/1951
      Concerning the Decline of the Labor Movement's Influence Upon Government..., 9/17/1951
      Browder Speaks: Article 12, Is Communism a New Faith?, Spadea Syndicate
    - 1952 (Box 49)
      Should America Be Returned to The Indians?, circa 1952
      An Examination of Whittaker Chambers' letter to his children, 1952
      A Reactionary Interpretation of History, 1952
    - 1952 Jan-Nov (Box 49)
      Letter To a Friend Concerning Togliatti's Article, 1/14/1952
      Meeting with Vito Marcantonio, memorandum, 1/29/1952
      Letter To a Friend Concerning 'Peaceful Co-Existence', 2/19/1952
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 3/8/1952
      Defense Policy in the Communist Party Cases, memorandum, 6/3/1952
      The Presidential Election of 1952, The Communist International[?], 11/1952
    - 1953 "Browder Speaks" (Box 49)
      Browder Speaks: Article 1, Treason Doth Never Prosper, Spadea Syndicate, 1953
      Browder Speaks: Article 2, Why I Am Not a Communist, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 3, Facts Behind the Browder case, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 4, The Government Saved the Communists, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 5, What Should America Do About the Former Communists, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 6, Roosevelt and Browder, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 7, McCarthyism in Soviet Russia, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 8, Comintern and Cominform, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 9, Georgi Dimitroff - Case History, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 10, Mau Tse-Tung and Tito, Spadea Syndicate
      Browder Speaks: Article 11, Behind the Peace Offensive, Spadea Syndicate
    - 1953 (Box 49)
      The Beria Bombshell -- Speculations are Hazardous, Spadea Syndicate, 1953
      Churchill Called the Turn, Spadea Syndicate, 1953
      Ex-Communist, 1953
      A letter From Earl Browder (re: Marguerite Higgins interview), 1953
    - 1953 Feb-Jul (Box 49)
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 2/1/1953
      Interview, Telepress TV Daily News Reel, 2/10/1953
      Letter to the editor, National Guardian, 3/3/1953
      Stalin's stroke, 3/3/1953
      What Follows The Era Of Stalin, 3/4/1953
      Is War Nearer?, The Nation, 3/14/1953
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 5/15/1953
      Some Critical Notes Concerning Isaac Deutscher's Russia: What Next?, review of Russia:What Next? by Isaac Deutscher, 7/1/1953
      Granville Hicks' Article in Harper's Magazine, memorandum, 7/22/1953
      Letter to the editor re:Granville Hicks' Article in Harper's Magazine, Harper's Magazine, 7/22/1953
    - 1954 (Box 49)
      Draft of Questions and Answers on Political Position, circa 1954
      How Can We Recognize Subversives?, 1954
      Some Problems In The Writing Of History, Review of European Communism by Franz Borkenau, 1954
      McCarthy Finally Gets the Low Down, 1954
    - 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 49)
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 1/4/1954
      Two articles about Browder's relationship to Soviet Communism, North American Newspaper Alliance, 1/11/1954
      Browder Calls His Ouster 'Best Thing Ever Happened", The Evening Star, Washinton, DC, 1/12/1954
      Browder Denounces Soviets, Buffalo Evening News, 1/13/1954
      McCarthyism at High Tide, 3/4/1954
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 4/19/1954
      Luncheon with Readers Digest Editors, memorandum, 6/7/1954
      Russification of the International Communist movement, memorandum, 6/20/1954
    - 1955 (Box 50)
      Communist Impact on American Literature 1930-1943, memorandum prepared for Theodore Draper [?], circa 1955?
      Communist Fronts in the Years 1930-1945, memorandum prepared for Theodore Draper ?, circa 1955?
      Attack on the Fund for the Republic by Fulton Lewis, Jr: Lawrence Spivak: and David Lawrence, for Wm. M. Goldsmith, 1955
    - 1955 Aug-Dec (Box 50)
      On The Role Of Organization In Politics (Essay VIII and IX), 8/20/1955
      Interview "A Fearless Approach", Sarah Lawrence College The Campus, 10/26/1955
      Relations Between the American Communist Party and the Communist International, memorandum prepared for Theodore Draper, 11/11/1955
      The American Communist Party Under Attack, memorandum prepared for Theodore Draper, 12/9/1955
    - 1956 (Box 50)
      Questions and answers re: Stalin and the CP, circa 1956
      Notes on the Revaluation of Stalin, 3/23/1956
      On Anti-Semitism in Soviet Russia (Letter to the editor), Midstream, 11/3/1956
    - 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 50)
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 1/13/1957
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 2/9/1957
      Letter to the editor, New York Times, 6/8/1957
    - 1958 (Box 50)
      A Study of the New Yugoslav Program, 1958
      My Visit to Beograd: What Interested Yugoslavs, 1958
      America's Changing Economic Problem, Review of International Affairs, 1958
      Socialism in America, 12/4/1958
    - 1959 (Box 50)
      Notes on the Origins of the Cold war, circa 1959
    - 1959 Mar-Aug (Box 50)
      Oakley C. Johnson's Article on Ruthenberg, to Philip Jaffe, 3/27/1959
      America's Changing Economic Problem, Review of International Affairs, Beograd, Yugoslavia, 8/1959
    - 1960 (Box 50)
      As Earl Browder Sees the Future of the Left in America, circa 1960
      Reminiscences of Social and Political Movements in the 1930s, circa 1960
      Socialism in America, St Antony's Papers, London, 1960
    - 1960 Feb-Jul (Box 50)
      Changes In the Communist World, North American Newspaper Alliance, 2/1960
      Commentary, 2/1960
      Letter to the editor, Saturday Review, 3/24/1960
      How Stalin Killed the American Communist Party, Harper's Magazine, 3/1960
      Before the American Presidential Nominations, Review of International Affairs, 7/1960
    - 1961 (Box 50)
      European Economy, circa 1961
      America's Road to Socialism, 8/19/1961
    - 1962 (Box 50)
      Book review: The Strangled Cry by John Strachey, Encounter, London, review of The Strangled Cry by John Strachey, 1962
      What Happened to American Socialism?, 3/1962
    - 1963 (Box 50)
      Notes for an article on the Sino-Soviet split, 1963
      Book review: M. N. Roy's Mission to China, Political Science Quarterly, by Robert C. North and Xenia J. Eudin, 1963
    - 1964 (Box 50)
      After the American Presidential Nominations, Review of International Affairs, 1964
    - 1966 (Box 50)
      Book review: Soviet Strategies in Southeast Asia by Charles B. McLane, Political Science Quarterly, 1966
    - 1967 (Box 50)
      Book review: Enemies and Friends by Lyman P. Van Slyke, Political Science Quarterly, 1967
    - 1969 (Box 50)
      Book review: Utopia and Reality by Betty Yerberg, Political Science Quarterly, 1969
    - Undated (Box 50)
      Letter to the editor, New Masses
      The Historical Background of the American Labor and Socialist Movements..., memorandum
      Historical Bases for American Power
      The Adventurer, The Call
      about Trotsky
      Book review: Imperialism and World Economy by Kikolai Bukharin
      About Soviet-American relations Post-War
      Mock radio broadcast
      Our Views: More on Father Coughlin's Program
      "Weekly Comment"
      Weekly Comment: Anglo-American Problems, 11/26/1944
      Weekly Comment: The Bretton Woods Conference
      Weekly Comment: Bullitt Rides Again, 9/10/1944
      Weekly Comment: Businessmen Need Wallace, 1/28/1945
      Weekly Comment: Capt. Lyttleton and Mr. Fleming, 6/25/1944
      Weekly Comment: CIO Must Uphold No-Strike Policy, 2/25/1944
      Weekly Comment: Communist ? So What ?, 9/24/1944
      Weekly Comment: The Communist Convention, 5/21/1944
      Weekly Comment: The Crisis in the Coalition, 12/31/1944
      Weekly Comment: The Crisis the Follows V-E Day, 5/20/1945
      Weekly Comment: Dewey and His Cabinet, 7?1944
      Weekly Comment: Dewey has a Grievance, 7/23/1944
      Weekly Comment: Dewey Reveals His Foreign Policy, 11/5/1944
      Weekly Comment: Dewey the Disruptionist, 10/22/1944
      Weekly Comment: Eric Johnston Renegs on His Book, 10/15/1944
      Weekly Comment: The GOP Against Teheran
      Weekly Comment: High Stakes in the UAW Referendum, 1/7/1945
      Weekly Comment: Hitler Also Almost Won, 11/19/1944
      Weekly Comment: Hitler's Chicago Newspaper, 5/28/1944
      Weekly Comment: Hitler's Slogan Works in Chicago, 4/1/1945
      Weekly Comment: How a Zero Can Become a Menace, 7/16/1944
      Weekly Comment: Hull Replaces Vandenberg, 5/13/1945
      Weekly Comment: India and the Colonial Question, 4/29/1945
      Weekly Comment: Is Senator Vandenberg Now Making U.S. Foreign Policy?, 5/6/1945
      Weekly Comment: Labor Relations at the Ford Plant, 5/7/1944
      Weekly Comment: Let's Not Forget the Campaign, 11/12/1944
      Weekly Comment: Lord Halifax Speaks Up, 12/3/1944
      Weekly Comment: Miss Thompson Goes to Europe, 3/25/1945
      Weekly Comment: More Unity and More Work, 1/7/1945
      Weekly Comment: Moscow-Teheran-Crimea-San Francisco, 2/17/1945
      Weekly Comment: Mr. Churchill Treads Dangerous Paths, 12/10/1944
      Weekly Comment: New Labor-Management Charter, 4/8/1945
      Weekly Comment: Overconfidence is Dangerous, 9/17/1944
      Weekly Comment: The President's Service Law Proposal, 1/14/1945
      Weekly Comment: The Second Front is Opened
      Weekly Comment: The San Francisco Conference [1], 5/27/1945